CURRICULUM VITAE

ANNE PRISCILLA NGIMA KARIUKI

Mobile number +254 728982068 Email annekariukilp@gmail.com

P.O BOX 453-10300, KERUGOYA

Professional Summary

Focused and resourceful Electrical Engineer with exceptional team leadership and quality assurance abilities. Able to work on multiple projects simultaneously and complete them on time and under budget. Have experience in commercial, industrial, residential and hospital projects. Meticulous attention to detail with regard to safety regulations and practices.

Core Qualifications

- Wide on-site electrical engineering experience
- Exceptional knowledge of electrical engineering principles and concepts
- High ability to conduct good working relationships with contractors and suppliers
- Sound grasp of electrical debugging systems and equipment

Experience

Intern

1/1/2022 - Present

Ministry of Public Works

Nairobi, Kenya

- Kept all clients architects and consultants updated on project progress.
- Provision of efficient CAD drawings.
- Conduct regular (daily) site visits.
- Supervised all subcontractor work to ensure compliance with client requirements.
- Assisted in resolving any technical issues, claims, and disputes arising.
- Maintained all safety and quality control project standards.
- Verified premium quality of all project construction materials.

• Documented and submitted all conducted work reports to clients.

Assistant Engineer

6/1/2016 - 4/11/2021

Sunnex Engineering Limited

Nairobi, Kenya

- Maintained good professional relationships with suppliers and contractors.
- Evaluated and resolved all project technical problems.
- Tested system for discrepancies in construction projects and objectives.
- Ensured project completion within budget and on schedule.
- Tested all products for correct installation and operation.

Electrical Engineer Attache

8/2/2013 - 31/12/2015

Comtec Networks Limited

Nairobi, Kenya

- Installation of telecoms equipment such as ODU, IDU, System/RF Modules, transmission cards, Combiners, jumper and IF cables, and RF Antennas.
- Commissioning, integrating and acceptance of the BTS/NodeB/eNodeB sites
- Configuration and Parameter changes on 2G/3G/4G sites
- Offering second line field support and troubleshooting for Field Operations engineers
- Conduct maintenance (preventative and curative) of 2G-3G NSN, NEC, Cambridge, Alcatel, Ericson and Ceragon transmission equipment in various cell sites/hubs.
- Provide fault/alarm clearance on BTS/NodeB and NOC
- Consistent monitoring, troubleshooting and reporting of all outages on network elements
- Creation of services like E1s and solves technical problems in enterprise links of customer network.

Education background

2007-2012: Masinde Muliro University

Bachelor of Technology Electrical and Communication Engineering

2002-2005: Don Bosco Girls High School

Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education

1997-2001: St Michael Girls Boarding

Kenya Certificate of Primary Education